<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Eda on Masood Sadat</title>
    <link>/tags/eda/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Eda on Masood Sadat</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/eda/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Explore Correlation Among Variables with Corrplot</title>
      <link>/2018/06/explore-correlation-among-variables-with-corrplot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/explore-correlation-among-variables-with-corrplot/</guid>
      <description>Exploring relationship among variables in a data set is never easier with corrplot package and function of the same name. corrplot takes in a correlation matrix and returns a visual representation of that correlation matrix.
Try it for yourself.
Install and load corrplot package  install.packages(&amp;quot;corrplot&amp;quot;) library(corrplot) Estimate correlation between all variables of mtcars dataset using cor, and then plot the correlations using corrplot(). You have to specify a method, and there are quite a few of them–here I demonstrate two of them: square and number  mat &amp;lt;- cor(mtcars) corrplot(mat, method = &amp;quot;square&amp;quot;) # corrplot(mat, method = &amp;quot;number&amp;quot;) To explore more, see the help (?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selection of Provinces for Monitoring in SAP 2018</title>
      <link>/2018/06/selection-of-provinces-for-monitoring-in-sap-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/selection-of-provinces-for-monitoring-in-sap-2018/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The Asia Foundation (TAF) employs a number of methods to ensure data quality for the Survey of the Afghan People (SAP). The most important quality controls are (1) third party monitoringy, and (2) logic tests. The third party monitoring is carried out on 10% of all surveys by an independent company, and 25% are subject to monitoring from the data collection company. The third party monitoring started in 2014, and since then Sayara Research has been the implementing partner for this activity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plot Missing Values</title>
      <link>/2018/05/plot-missing-values/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/plot-missing-values/</guid>
      <description>In this post, we will explore visdat package to visualize missing values. Then, we will recreate a similar plot using ggplot2 package. Next, using the ggplot2 method, we will visualize other numeric or character values in a dataset. Finally, using the ggplot2 method, we will create a custom function that will plot any value in any dataset.
 There are many ways to inspect and find about missing values in a dataset.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>