<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Masood Sadat</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Masood Sadat</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Build a Website with R, blogdown, Hugo, and netlify.com</title>
      <link>/2018/06/build-a-website-with-r-blogdown-hugo-and-netlify.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/build-a-website-with-r-blogdown-hugo-and-netlify.com/</guid>
      <description>One of the coolest things I have learned in R recently is creating a website with blogdown package. The blogdown websites are created and maintained from within R mostly, which is the best part about it if you are a R user. There are many sources that provide details and reasons for using blogdown, so I will not dwell on that. Instead, I am going to provide a brief and to-the-point tutorial on how to start your website with R and blogdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Tutorial for Analysing Survey of the Afghan People in R</title>
      <link>/2018/06/a-tutorial-for-analysing-survey-of-the-afghan-people-in-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/a-tutorial-for-analysing-survey-of-the-afghan-people-in-r/</guid>
      <description>1 About the Survey of the Afghan People Since 2006, The Asia Foundation conducts the Survey of the Afghan People, a nationally-representative annual survey. The Survey reflects perceptions about a broad range of topics including security, development, governance, service delivery, women’s rights, and migration. The Survey is broadly used by policy makers, academics, non-governmental organizations working in and on Afghanistan. The Foundation make the Survey’s data public on its website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plot Missing Values</title>
      <link>/2018/05/plot-missing-values/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/plot-missing-values/</guid>
      <description>In this post, we will explore visdat package to visualize missing values. Then, we will recreate a similar plot using ggplot2 package. Next, using the ggplot2 method, we will visualize other numeric or character values in a dataset. Finally, using the ggplot2 method, we will create a custom function that will plot any value in any dataset.
 There are many ways to inspect and find about missing values in a dataset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basics of GitHub Through Command Line</title>
      <link>/2018/05/basics-of-github-through-command-line/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/basics-of-github-through-command-line/</guid>
      <description>Create account and repository on github.com Go to github.com and create an account. Once, account is created, create a repository in Repositories tab and click on the green button New. The following page opens.
 NOTE: A repository is something like a project folder.
   Copy repository URL After a new repository is created, copy the clone url link. This link is used to clone the repository from server to the computer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perceptions About Electricity in Afghanistan: Insights From the Survey of the Afghan People</title>
      <link>/2018/05/perceptions-about-electricity-in-afghanistan-insights-from-the-survey-of-the-afghan-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/perceptions-about-electricity-in-afghanistan-insights-from-the-survey-of-the-afghan-people/</guid>
      <description>About This analysis uses the Survey of the Afghan People data, an annual survey of perceptions from a nationally representative sample of Afghans. The survey has collected attitudes and perceptions uninterruptedly since 2006, with over 97,000 Afghans taking part. The the latest survey report here, or download the raw data here.  Awareness of Government Supplied Electricity Projects  Key Questions: x11as. I am going to read a list of projects that may or may not have been implemented in your area.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>