<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Afghanistan on Masood Sadat</title>
    <link>/categories/afghanistan/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Afghanistan on Masood Sadat</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/afghanistan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Tutorial for Analysing Survey of the Afghan People in R</title>
      <link>/2018/06/a-tutorial-for-analysing-survey-of-the-afghan-people-in-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/06/a-tutorial-for-analysing-survey-of-the-afghan-people-in-r/</guid>
      <description>1 About the Survey of the Afghan People Since 2006, The Asia Foundation conducts the Survey of the Afghan People, a nationally-representative annual survey. The Survey reflects perceptions about a broad range of topics including security, development, governance, service delivery, women’s rights, and migration. The Survey is broadly used by policy makers, academics, non-governmental organizations working in and on Afghanistan. The Foundation make the Survey’s data public on its website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Perceptions About Electricity in Afghanistan: Insights From the Survey of the Afghan People</title>
      <link>/2018/05/perceptions-about-electricity-in-afghanistan-insights-from-the-survey-of-the-afghan-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/05/perceptions-about-electricity-in-afghanistan-insights-from-the-survey-of-the-afghan-people/</guid>
      <description>About This analysis uses the Survey of the Afghan People data, an annual survey of perceptions from a nationally representative sample of Afghans. The survey has collected attitudes and perceptions uninterruptedly since 2006, with over 97,000 Afghans taking part. The the latest survey report here, or download the raw data here.  Awareness of Government Supplied Electricity Projects  Key Questions: x11as. I am going to read a list of projects that may or may not have been implemented in your area.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>